<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitHub on Peg&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://pegeaton.github.io/tags/github/</link>
    <description>Recent content in GitHub on Peg&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 01:12:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pegeaton.github.io/tags/github/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part 2: Dive Deeper into GitHub Actions</title>
      <link>https://pegeaton.github.io/post/ninja/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 01:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pegeaton.github.io/post/ninja/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s take a hands-on approach and walk-through creating the hello world program and GitHub Actions workflow together. The GitHub documentation (https://docs.github.com/) is available as a reference as needed.
In this exercise you will create a GitHub repository containing three files: README.md, hello.go, and hello-action.yml. The file structure is shown in the following diagram:
  Samples Repository Structure   1. Create a GitHub Account Create a GitHub account, if you have not done so already.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part 1: GitHub Actions in the Modern Apps Ninja Repository</title>
      <link>https://pegeaton.github.io/post/ninja/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 01:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pegeaton.github.io/post/ninja/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>In this blog series, we explore automated workflows supporting the Modern Apps Ninja program. Modern Apps Ninja program administrators and members are encouraged to explore automation and CI/CD to improve the delivery of content and provide experiential learning for community members. The series outline follows:
 Part 1 introduces the Modern Apps Ninja GitHub Repository, GitHub Actions, the GitHub Actions Marketplace, and demonstrates GitHub Actions Ecosystem workflows as leveraged by the Modern Apps Ninja administrators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
